http://www.archadeckfranchise.com/privacy-policy/

H1 Content Goes Here
H2 Content Goes Here
Paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content
paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content
paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content
paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content paragraph content
It's more than a mission. It's a code of values
Archadeck is part of the Outdoor Living Brands family of franchise brands.
Outdoor Living Brands is a franchise corporation dedicated to the outdoor
living category and currently includes the following companies:
Our mission at Archadeck is to celebrate outdoor living by enriching lives
through our proven franchise brand. For our valued clients, we do this
by designing and delivering beautiful, functional and innovative outdoor
living environments that meet their lifestyle needs.
The Outdoor Living Brands Code of Values shows how our mission will be
accomplished. These core values define our culture and our relationships
with our franchise partners. We communicate our core values in the phrase,
“LIVE WELL.”
Live Well
Lifestyle
Helping our clients celebrate the good life outdoors.
Integrity
At every touch point in our service, products, attitude and communication,
it defines us.
Visionary
Innovative thinking in all capacities, from new markets to new outdoor
living trends.
Enriching Lives
Helping our franchise partners meet personal and lifestyle goals.
World Class
Passionately delivering unparalleled products and client service.
Enthusiasm
It’s why we get up in the morning.
Leadership
Leading by example and attracting those who take ownership and accountability.
Laughter
Without laughter, it would just be work.
Learn More
"We've been able to consistently grow anywhere from a 25% - 50% growth rate for 5 or 6 years. Now we're in the position to go to the next level."
- Ben Wood
Privacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is very important to us, and the following will inform you of the information that we, Archadeck Franchising, may collect from you, and how it is used. By using our website, www.archadeckfranchise.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.Information CollectionWe may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Information UseWe use the collected information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests for information, and providing customer support.SecurityWe follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.If we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.SharingWe will not sell or otherwise provide the information we collect to outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass email marketing.We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our companyProtect and defend the rights or property of our Website and related propertiesIdentify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing our Website or its related propertiesPlease keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion boards, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.LinksThis Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.ConsentBy using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at
(804) 374-9736 or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 2426 Old Brick Rd, Glen Allen, VA 23060.
Making Outdoor Living Dreams Come True
Our services exceed client expectations and bring in repeat business.
Learn More
Become Your Local Deck Expert
Learn More About the Franchise Opportunities We Offer
First Name
Please enter your first name.
Last Name
Please enter your last name.
Email
Please enter your email address.
This isn't a valid email address.
Phone
This isn't a valid phone number.
City
Please enter your city.
State
Please enter your state.
Zip
Please enter your zip.
Submit
The typical investment to open a franchise ranges from $100,000 - $150,000.
